Guide to the American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), District Council 1707 Records WAG.298
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series II: General Administrative and Locals Files, 1950-2006
  - Election Objection: AFSCME Election Department--Hearing Transcript, Jun 25, 1992 (I) (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Election Objection: AFSCME Election Department--Hearing Transcript, Jun 25, 1992 (II) (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Election Objection: AFSCME Election Department--Hearing Transcript, Jun 25, 1992 (III) (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Employee Leave Requests, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Executive Board: Constitutional Admendments, 1986-1988 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Executive Board: Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Executive Board: Correspondence, 1998-2000 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Executive Board: Correspondence, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Executive Board: Member List, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Executive Board: Memoranda, 1997-2001 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Family and Medical Leave Act, Undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Field Services Department: Reports, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Finance Committee, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Financial Records: Acting Fiscal Affairs Director Memos, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Financial Records: ADAPT Northwest (South Africa), 2001 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Financial Records: AFL-CIO, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Financial Records: AFSCME, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Financial Records: American Arbitration Association, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Financial Records: American Red Cross of Greater New York, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Financial Records: Association for the Help of Retarded Children, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Financial Records: Audit, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Financial Records: Black Women's Leadership Conference, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Financial Records: Board of Directors Presentation, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Financial Records: Bolton-St. John's Inc., 2001 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Financial Records: The Chief-Leader, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Financial Records: Children and Families for Green (Political Action), 2001 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Financial Records: Chinese-American Planning Council, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Financial Records: Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU), 2001 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Financial Records: Contingencies, 1999-2001 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Financial Records: Correspondence, 1997-2001 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Financial Records: DC 1707 Health and Insurance Fund, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Financial Records: DC 1707 Professional Staff Employees Retirement Fund, 1983-1986 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Financial Records: DC 1707 Professional Staff Employees Retirement Fund, 1987-1989 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Financial Records: DC 1707 Professional Staff Employees Retirement Fund, 1990-1993 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Financial Records: Financial Meeting--Nov 30, 2000, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Financial Records: General, 1974-1997 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Financial Records: Investment, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Financial Records: Notes, Ephemera, 1997, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Financial Records: Pride at Work Convention, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Financial Records: Rent Negotiations, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Financial Records: Reports, 1973-1982 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Financial Records: Reports, 1983-1986 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Financial Records: Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Financial Records: Reports, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Financial Records: Reports, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Financial Records: Reports, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Financial Records: Reports, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Financial Records: Reports--Accountant's Assembly, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Financial Records: Reports (Income Statements), 1996-1999 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Financial Records: Reports--Budget Comparisons/Projections, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Financial Records: Reports (Income Statements), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Financial Records: Reports, 2001-2002 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Financial Records: Reports, 2003-2005 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Financial Records: Staff Employees Retirement Plan, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Financial Records: Statements, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Requests, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - General Membership Meetings, 1964-1973 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Government and Civic Employees Organizing Committee, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Health and Safety Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - International Foundation of Employee Benefit Plans: Conference, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Labor: General, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Latino Affairs Committee, 1985-1992, undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Legal: Leibowitz and Mars LLP, 1998-2000 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Legal: Sipser, Weinstock, Harper and Dorn, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Long Term Disability Certificate, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Monthly Reports, Jan - Apr 1998 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Monthly Reports, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - New York State Reports, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Not-for-Profits/Non-Profits Report, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Notes, 1996, undated (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Office and Professional Employees International Union (OPEIU), 1997, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Office Renovations, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Organizing, 1985, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Organizing, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Organizing, 1999-2000 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Political Action Committee, 1992-1997 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Political Action Committee, 1998-2000, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Political Action Conference, 1994, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Press Releases, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Professional Staff/Professional Employees Union, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Public Employees Organized to Promote Legislative Equality (PEOPLE) Committee, 1995-2000 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Rallies and Demonstrations, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Shop Assignment Visits, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Shop Assignment Visits, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Shop Assignment Visits, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Social Service Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Staff Meeting, Apr - May 1993 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Staff Meetings: Assistant Directors, 1987-1989, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Staff Meetings: Minutes, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Staff Telephone Extensions, [1998] (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Weekly Schedules, 1997-2000 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Women's Affairs Committee, 1997-2000 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Local 95: General Administrative, 1989-1996 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Local 95: Executive Board Meeting, Unidentified Meeting, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Local 95: Head Start Employees Welfare Fund, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Local 95: Head Start Employees Welfare Fund--Trustee Board Meetings, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Local 95: Head Start Employees Welfare Fund--Trustee Board Meeting, Feb 12, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Local 95: Head Start Employees Welfare Fund--[Trustee Board Meeting?], [Sep 1997] (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Local 95: Head Start Employees Welfare Fund--Trustee Board Meeting, Feb 5, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Local 95: Head Start Employees Welfare Fund--Trustee Board Meeting (I), Nov 17, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Local 95: Head Start Employees Welfare Fund--Trustee Board Meeting (II), Nov 17, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Local 95: Head Start Employees Welfare Fund--Trustee Board Meeting, Mar 10, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Local 95: Head Start Employees Welfare Fund--Trustee Board Meeting, May 27, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Local 95: Head Start Employees Welfare Fund--Trustee Board Meeting, Nov 17, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Local 95: Head Start Employees Welfare Fund--Trustee Board Meeting, Feb 16, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Local 95: Head Start Employees Welfare Fund--Trustee Board Meeting, May 4, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Local 107: Correspondence, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Local 205: Agencies, 1978-1981 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Local 205: AFSCME, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Local 205: AFSCME--PEOPLE Fund Raising Campaign Kit, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Local 205: Arbitration, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Local 205: Awards Dinner/Dance, 2001, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Local 205: Board and Committee Members, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Local 205: Communication Committee, 1979-1982 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Local 205: Communication Committee Meetings, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Local 205: Correspondence, Memoranda, 1978-1981 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Local 205: Day Care Council Local 205--Welfare Fund/Group Legal Fund, 1986-1990 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Local 205: Day Care Council Local 205--Welfare Fund/Group Legal Fund, 1989-1991 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Local 205: Day Care Council Local 205--Welfare Fund/Group Legal Fund (I), 1990-1992 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Local 205: Day Care Council Local 205--Welfare Fund/Group Legal Fund (II), 1990-1992 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Local 205: Day Care Council Local 205--Welfare Fund/Group Legal Fund (I), 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Local 205: Day Care Council Local 205--Welfare Fund/Group Legal Fund (II), 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Local 205: Day Care Council Local 205--Welfare Fund/Group Legal Fund, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Local 205: Day Care Council of New York--Bargaining, 1970-1988 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Local 205: Day Care Council of New York--Job Descriptions, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Local 205: DC 1707 Constitution, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Local 205: Elections, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Local 205: Elections for Delegates to AFSCME International Conventions, 1978-1980 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Local 205: Ephemera, 1979-1984, undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Local 205: Event Programs, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Local 205: Executive Board Meetings, 1977-1991 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Local 205: Financial Documents, 1978-1983, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Local 205: Flyers, Handouts, 1979-1996, undated (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Local 205: General Membership Meetings, 1980-1983 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Local 205: Grievances, Sep 1997-Jan 1998 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Local 205: Grievances, Feb-Mar 1998 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Local 205: Grievances, Apr-Jun 1998 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Local 205: Grievances, Jul-Dec 1998 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Local 205: Legislation, 1974-1980 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Local 205: Legislation (I), 1974-1984 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Local 205: Legislation (II), 1974-1984 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Local 205: Legislation, [1983]-1986 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Local 205: Legislative Committee, 1977-1979 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Local 205: Legislative Committee--Correspondence, 1979-1982 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Local 205: Legislative Committee--Meetings, 1976-1982 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Local 205: Meeting Minutes--Alvin Turner File, 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Local 205: Meetings--Other, 1978-1980 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Local 205: Members, Undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Local 205: Negotiating Session(s), 1980, undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Local 205: New York City Day Care Direct Lease Program Report, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Local 205: New York City Government, 1984, undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Local 205: New York State Worksite Child Care Centers--Boards of Directors, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Local 205: Programs, 1980-1984 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Local 205: Public Employees Organized to Promote Legislative Equality (PEOPLE), Undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Local 205: Shop Stewards Meetings, 1979-1983 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Local 215: AFSCME, 1974, 1997-1998 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Local 215: AFSCME, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Local 215: AFSCME, 1999-2000, undated (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Local 215: Agencies, 1994-1998 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Local 215: Agencies--Agency/Shop Steward Listing, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Local 215: Agencies--AFSCME Dues Reporting Forms, 1997, undated (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Local 215: Agencies--Bargaining, 1981-1994 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Local 215: Agencies--Bargaining, 1991-1999 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Local 215: Agencies--Bargaining--Federation Group Work Agencies, 1985-1995 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Local 215: Agencies--Bargaining--Jewish Board of Family and Children's Services/Jewish Child Care Association, 1985-2000 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Local 215: Agencies--Bargaining--New York Association for New Americans, 1991-2000 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Local 215: Agencies--Bargaining--United Jewish Federation of MetroWest, [1993]-2000 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Local 215: Agencies--Correspondence, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Local 215: Agencies--Staff Representatives Reports, 1993-2000, undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Local 215: Arthur Tate Case--Misappropriation of Funds, 1996-1997 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Local 215: Board Meeting Material, [Jun, Dec 1999] (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Local 215: Correspondence, 1985-2000 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Local 215: DC 1707, 1993-2000 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Local 215: Election Materials, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Local 215: Ephemera, Undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Local 215: Financial Records, 1979-2000 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Local 215: General Administrative, 1994-2000 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Local 215: Grievances/Grievance Committee, 1985-2000 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Local 215: Judicial Panel and New York State Supreme Court Cases (Internal Disputes), 1992 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Local 215: Leadership Training Program, 1981, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Local 215: [Leadership Training], 1997 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Local 215: Leadership Training Program--Shop Stewards, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Local 215: Local 215 Executive Board, 1998-2000 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Local 215: Meetings/Workshops/Events, 1995-2000 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Local 215: Membership Meetings, 1993-1999, undated (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Local 215: New York City Central Labor Council, 1999-2000 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Local 215: New York Labor Party/Labor Party, 1997-1999, undated (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Local 215: New York State Reports, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Local 215: Notes, 2000, undated (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Local 215: Petition to DC 1707 for More Staff Representatives, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Local 215: Retreats, 1995-1999 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Local 215: Steward Manuals/Training, 1974-1993 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Local 253: Agencies--Correspondence, 1997-998 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Local 253: Bargaining, 1997-1998 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Local 253: Correspondence--Elections, 1998-2000 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Local 253: Correspondence--General, 1996-2000 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Local 253: Grievances, 1995-2000 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Local 253: Meetings--Notices, 1996-1999 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Local 253: Miriam E. Aguayo Statement, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Local 389: Agencies--Contracts, Contact List, 1998-2003 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Local 389: Agencies--Correspondence, Memoranda, 1980-2000 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Local 389: Constitution, 1981-2004 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Local 389: Contacts--Board of Estimate, Human Resources Administration (HRA), Undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Local 389: Correspondence, 1978-2004 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Local 389: Correspondence--Memoranda, Flyers, 1978-1999 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Local 389: Correspondence--Memoranda, Flyers, 2000-2005, undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Local 389: Education, 1989, undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Local 389: Election Materials, 1995-1998 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Local 389: Ephemera, 1996-2002 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Local 389: Executive Board Meetings, 1998-2002 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Local 389: Executive Board Meetings, 2003-2005 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Local 389: Financial Records, 2002-2004 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Local 389: Financial Records--Health and Welfare Fund, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Local 389: Grievances/Grievance Forms, 1990-2003 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Local 389: Home Care Employees Health and Welfare Fund--Trustees Meetings, Reports, 1988-1990 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Local 389: Home Care Employees Health and Welfare Fund--Trustees Meetings, Reports, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Local 389: Home Care Employees Health and Welfare Fund--Trustees Meetings, Reports, 1990-1991 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Local 389: Home Care Employees Health and Welfare Fund--Trustees Meetings, Reports, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Local 389: Home Care Employees Pension and Health and Welfare Funds--Trustees Meeting, Jul 31, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Local 389: Home Care Employees Pension and Health and Welfare Funds--Trustees Meeting, Consultant's Report, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Local 389: Home Care Employees Pension and Health and Welfare Funds--Trustees Meeting, Correspondence, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Local 389: Home Care Registry Bill, 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Local 389: Home Care Work Group, 1990-1991 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Local 389: Home Care Workers Report, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Local 389: Human Resources Administration (HRA)--Hearing on Home Care Services Program and Protective Services for Adults, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Local 389: International Foundation--Annual Employee Benefits Conference of Employee Benefit Plans, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Local 389: International Foundation of Employee Benefits Plans--Fraud Prevention Institute, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Local 389: Labor Council for Latin American Advancement (LCLAA)--Conferences/Conventions, 2004-2006 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Local 389: Labor Council for Latin American Advancement (LCLAA)--NYC Central Chapter, 1998-1999 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Local 389: Labor Council for Latin American Advancement (LCLAA)--NYC Central Chapter, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Local 389: Leadership Conference, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Local 389: Life Insurance Fund, 2002-2004, undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Local 389: Living Wage Bill--New York City, 1987, 2001-2003, undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Local 389: Living Wage Bill--Westchester, 2002, undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Local 389: Long Island Office, 2000-2001 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Local 389: Membership Meetings, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Local 389: Negotiations--Jewish Association for Services for the Aged (JASA), Association for Services for the Aged, Services for the Aged, 1984-1988 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Local 389: Office and Professional Employees International Union (OPEIU), Local 153, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Local 389: Organizing, 1986, undated (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Local 389: Personal Care Level I (Housekeeper Program)--NYC Medicaid, 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Local 389: Wages and Benefits, [1998] (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Local 1881: Memoranda, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Retirees Chapter: AFSCME, 1983-1998, undated (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Retirees Chapter: Benefits, 1990, undated (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Retirees Chapter: Clippings, 1979-1996, undated (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Retirees Chapter: Congress of Senior Citizens of Greater New York, 1996, undated (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Retirees Chapter: Constitution, 1980-1989, undated (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Retirees Chapter: Correspondence, 1980-1999 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Retirees Chapter: Correspondence--Memoranda, 1995-1998 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Retirees Chapter: DC 1707, 1982-1997, undated (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Retirees Chapter: Ephemera, Notes, 1987-1996, undated (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Retirees Chapter: Events (Non-AFSCME, DC 1707), [1980-1996] (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Retirees Chapter: Excursions, 1995-1997, undated (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Retirees Chapter: Flyers, Handouts, 1981-1998, undated (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Retirees Chapter: Health Care, 1986-1997, undated (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Retirees Chapter: Human Services Providers Advisory Committee, 1990, undated (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Retirees Chapter: Meetings, 1980-1983 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Retirees Chapter: Meetings, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Retirees Chapter: Meetings, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Retirees Chapter: Meetings, Jan-May 1986 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Retirees Chapter: Meetings, Jun-Dec 1986 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Retirees Chapter: Meetings, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Retirees Chapter: Meetings, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Retirees Chapter: Meetings, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Retirees Chapter: Meetings, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Retirees Chapter: Meetings, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Retirees Chapter: Meetings, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Retirees Chapter: Meetings, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Retirees Chapter: Meetings, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Retirees Chapter: Meetings, 1995-1997 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Retirees Chapter: Meetings--Notices, Memoranda, 1981-2000 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Retirees Chapter: Members, 1985-1998 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Retirees Chapter: National Council of Senior Citizens/New York State Council of Senior Citizens, 1981-1996, undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Retirees Chapter: New York City/State, Undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Retirees Chapter: Notices to New Retirees, 1981-1996, undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Retirees Chapter: Retirement Planning, 1982, undated (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Retirees Chapter: Southern Poverty Law Center, 1993-1995 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Floppy disk (Women's Affairs Committee), Undated (Box 47)
- Series III: Agency Files, 1947-2007
  Agency files document Local 1707/DC 1707's relationships with its members' workplaces. Bargaining material includes contracts, agreements and other signed documents, negotiation material, correspondence and memoranda, and notes relating to the collective bargaining process. Grievance files document individual and group grievances against employers. Personnel files generally contain information about workplace staff, hiring, firing, and positions. General Administrative material includes meeting notices, correspondence, and other administrative items. DC 1707 Staff Representative files contain copies of outgoing staff representative correspondence and memoranda involving administrative issues, including bargaining, grievances, and meetings. Affiliated locals are listed in parenthesis when known.
  - Abbott House, Inc.: Bargaining (Local 215), [1984] (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Altro Health and Rehabilitation Services: Bargaining (Local 215), 1975-1977 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - American Committee on Africa: Bargaining (Local 107), 1993 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - American Committee on Africa: Grievance--Sandy Boyer (Local 107), 1995 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - American Friends of the Hebrew University, Inc.: Bargaining (Local 107), 1996 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - American Jewish Committee: Grievances, Correspondence (Local 107), 1995-1996 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - American Jewish Congress: Bargaining (Local 107), 1995-1996 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Amit Women, Inc.: Bargaining (Local 107), 1996 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Angel Guardian Home: Bargaining (Local 215), 1995-1996 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Angel Guardian Home: Grievance (Local 215), 1995-1999 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Associated YM and YWHAs of Greater New York: Bargaining (Local 215), 1959-1975 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Associated YM and YWHAs of Greater New York: Grievance (Local 215), 1964 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Association for Services for the Aged: Bargaining (Local 389), 2001 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Association for the Help of Retarded Children: Bargaining (Local 253), [1986], 1995-2000 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Association for the Help of Retarded Children: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 253), 1995-2000 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Bank Street College of Education: Bargaining (Local 253), 1961-1968 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Bank Street College of Education: Bargaining (Local 253), 1969-1976 (Box 17, Folder 32)